SERHL HEREDNICHENKO

ABOUT ME

I AM DATA ENGINEER WITH 2 YEARS EXPERIENCE IN IT. WORKING WITH DATABASES (MYSQL), USING PYTHON FOR CALCULATIONS, OPTIMISATION AND CREATION OF NEW DATABASES.I WANT TO DEVELOP MYSELF IN DATA SCIENCE AND LAW-REGULATION WITH BLOCKCHAIN-BASED SMARTCONTRACTS.

SKILLS

PYTHON (PYSPARK, PYTORCH, NUMPY, PANDAS) SQL **DOCKER** GIT **POWER BI** HTML, CSS, TYPESCRIPT **GOOGLE CLOUD SOLIDITY**

LANGUAGES

UKRAINIAN: NATIVE ENGLISH: INTERMEDIATE RUSSIAN: NATIVE CZECH: INTERMEDIATE

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Engineer in Fozzy Group

project «Temabit» | January 2021 - February 2022

- creating microsoftware solutions for relational databases;
- $\mbox{\sc API}$ development for integration to system;
- connecting new sources of data;
- preparing window dressing;
- troubleshoot data issues and performance tuning of Spark jobs;
- design and develop Data Pipeline processes for the Data Architecture lifecycle;
- maintain and support existing report and data products;
- be up to date on various data processing, storage, analysis and reporting tools, their possibilities and limitations;
- collaborate and work alongside with Data Architects, Data Engineer, Data Analysts and other teammate;

Data Analyst in Beetroot

project «Upptec » | May 2020 - January 2021

- creating new blocks for databases;
- support old database parties;
- visualisation data with Power BI; - teaching interns to work with data

EDUCATION

CONTACTS

KYIV, UKRAINE 0502613682 | 0636767056 IAMCHERYA@GMAIL.COM HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/XOROWEE HTTPS://WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/SERGEY-CHEREDNICHENKO-B89B54173

Poltava's University of Economics and Trade

Bachelor's deegree (law) | 2014-2017